

# **Kevin Kimmett**

# **Product Designer**

Over the past 26 years, I have had the opportunity to develop my digital design craft into a wide range of disciplines. By gaining plenty of insight into how a user interacts with a product I am able to create approachable and user-friendly solutions.

### About Me

### Some of my skills are ...

Problem solving, Critical thinking, UI/UX Design, User Research & Testing, Collaboration, Prototyping, Visual Design, Responsive Design

#### I'm most proud of ...

Conceptualizing and desiging CBC's first iPhone and iPad apps for CBC Radio and Hockey Night in Canada

### I'm proficient in ...

Figma, Sketch, Invision, Adobe Creative Suite

#### I also have experience with ...

Webflow, Front-end design, Accessibility, Designing for children

### Education

### **Graphic Design Program**

George Brown College 1997 - 2000

## Experience

## **Senior Product Designer**

CBC/Radio-Canada (2005 - present)

My current role is Product Designer for Native Apps & Voice Platforms where I work with a team to help define the experience and interface of our products. I enjoy being able to work in a place where I can design new experiences for an extremely diverse industry.

My daily tasks also include user research, developing concepts, creating prototypes, high-fidelity designs and asset creation, and researching current design trends in emerging digital environments.

## Senior Web Designer

Mindblossom (2004 - 2005)

Created impactful web marketing strategies for Zip.ca, Workopolis, and Web Perspectives, driving significant revenue growth. Led a team, directed design, and executed Flash and HTML development.

## **Web Designer**

CHUM Television (2000 - 2004)

Collaborated with content producers to elevate online branding, improve web usability, and create impactful internet marketing campaigns. Translated content into visually engaging Flash ads for multiple channels, amplifying audience appreciation.

# Web Designer

CIBC (1998 - 2000)

Transformed policy communication for a 40,000-strong employee base, collaborating with partners to design, develop, and test an intranet prototype.